# Adrian Egea

# Computer Science

07745862541 | adrian.egea.comenge@gmail.com

website http://adrianecom.github.io/portfolio/

github https://github.com/AdrianECom

linkedIn https://es.linkedin.com/in/adrián-egea-comenge-8a4902b9

#### **Personal Summary**

Game programming related topics are my passion, such as, game engine programming, graphics programming (OpenGL), gameplay programming or physics programming. I have real passion for what I study, I love programming and learning about game programming.

My strongest skills are my patient, my will and my creativity, they allowed me to become self-learner and code my own 2D Game Engine. I am also a proficient team player, hard worker and creative.

Thanks you for reading, I truly hope you like my experience.

## Work experience

**Cl3ver** Jun 2017 - Nov 2017 (6 months)

Graphics Programmer

Responsible for the development of Oculus Rift application with C++ and OpenGL and Creation of plugins for Rhino and Sketchup.

3D, Graphics, Render, WebGL, OpenGL, OpenCV,

HTC vibe, Oculus, JS, NodeJS, Electron.

Tretanto Dec 2015 - Apr 2016 (5 months)

Web programmer

Responsible for the development of Wallfer.com (social network) backend and some parts of frontend.

JS, JQuery, AngularJS, Android, REST API, Social Networks building,

PHP, Symfony2 Framework, Doctrine, MySQL.

Neosistec Feb 2015 - Apr 2015 (3 months)

Android programmer

Internship oriented to learn Android.

Java, XML, MySQL.

#### **Skills**

- C/C++
- JavaScript
- CMake

Git

Java

• LaTeX

HTML

- OpenGLWebGL
- Linux
- GLSL
- LibGDX
- Game Engine
   Architecture and internals
- Artificial Intelligence (AI) for Video Games
- Real-time rendering
- Real-time Physics / Collisions

### **Projects**

[ Final Year Project ] JavaScript + WebGL 2D Game Engine July 2013 - May 2017

This Game Engine is developed as end-of-degree project and it is written in Javascript, WebGL and GLSL.

https://github.com/AdrianECom/ThiefEngine

C++ / OpenGL Game Engine Nov 2017 - Present

Reading "Game Engine Architecture" from Jason Gregory and improving my C++ / OpenGL skills by writing a Game Engine.

https://github.com/AdrianECom/DruidEngine

Artificial Intelligence for Video Games. Java + LibGDX April 2016 - July 2016

University Project. Artificial Intelligence for Video Games. Java + LibGDX. (Basic Steering, Delegate Steering, Group Steering, Flocking, State Machines, Pathfinding).

https://github.com/AdrianECom/Al-Videogames-2016

#### Education

BSc (Hons) Computer Science degree. (2:1) 2012 - 2017

University of Murcia – um.es/informatica/

SCRUM Manager Certificate (level Expert) May 2015

SCRUM Manager - scrummanager.net

#### Extra Information

- Languages: Spanish (mother tongue).
- Full driving licence.
- Elegible to work in the UK.